瑞秋
Oh! Hey, Rach.
我只是来...
l was just coming over here to....
我没必要骗你  你都搬走了
Wait, l don't have to lie to you, you don't live here anymore.
我来偷吃他们的东西  你呢
l'm eating their food. What are you doing?
罗斯跟我妹约会
Ross is on a date with my sister.
窗帘都已经拉上两个半小时了
They shut the drapes two and a half hours ago.
原来我们能泡你妹妹哦
l didn't know we could date your sister.
乔伊  我们知道你偷吃我们东西
Joey, we know you steal our food.
不用了
l'm good.
窗帘还没拉开吗
Are their drapes still closed?
对  其实最应该拉上窗帘的
Yeah. You know who should've shut theirs drapes.
是隔两户的变态老夫妇
that perverted couple two doors over.
-那是情趣秋千吗  -别问了吧
- ls that a swing? - Oh, don't even ask.
真没想到罗斯会去泡瑞秋的妹妹
l can't believe Ross is going out with Rachel's sister.
想当年钱德勒勒跟我妹亲热
When Chandler made out with my sister,
我气了他十年
l was mad at him for 10 years.
-那才五年前的事  -对  还要气你五年呢
- That was five years ago. - You got five years left.
-乔伊... -你想再加一年吗
- Joey- -  - Want to make it six?
罗斯  你好吗
Oh, Ross, hey. Hi, how are you?
-你在这里啊  -不错
- There you are. - Great.
一杯咖啡
Can l get a cup of coffee?
昨晚的约会怎样啊
So how was your big date last night?
还不错  很开心
lt was okay. lt was fun.
是吗  开心啊  太好了
Yeah, lt was fun? Great.
所以...  你们"一拍即合"了吗
So..so did you guys hit it off?
应该吧
l guess so.
所以你们有怎样吗
So...so did anything happen?
听说你们把窗帘拉上了啊
Beacase rumor has it you guys shut the drapes.
没  我们没怎样
No. No. Nothing happened.
拉窗帘只是要放我最爱的化石幻灯片
l shut the drapes to show her slides of my favorite fossils.
幻灯片
Oh, slides!
所以你们真的没怎样
So really nothing happened.
我们可以有怎样
Something could've happened.
她很喜欢我的幻灯片
She really dug my slides.
-而且她绝对有对我放电  -放电啊
- And she was definitely giving me the vibe. -Vibe...
是"别再给我看三叶虫照片"的电吗
Was it the "please don't show me another picture of a trilobite" vibe?
总之
Anyway....
要是她不喜欢我  为什么要再约我
lf she wasn't into me, why would she ask me out again?
-她又约你了吗  -对
- She asked you out again? - Yeah.
明天晚上
Tomorrow night.
情人节
Valentine's Day.
一年当中最浪漫的日子
The most romantic day of the year.
谁晓得会怎样
Who knows what could happen.
到时拉窗帘  可能就不是放幻灯片哦
l might not be shutting my drapes to show her my slides.
-你懂我意思吧  -好好好好
- if you know what I mean? - Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
我懂我懂我懂
l got it, l got it.
我不能接受你跟我妹交往
l can't go with the "you and my sister" thing, ok?
真接受不了
I just can't!
那样太奇怪了  好吗
lt's just too weird, all right?
一想到你们在一起我就捉狂
l imagine the two of you together, and I freak out.
-我会疯掉  我受不了  -行行行
- lt just freaks me out. l can't do it! - Okay.
-我真的受不了  -别激动  没事的
- l can't do it! - lt's okay.
好啦
lt's okay.
如果你接受不了  我就不跟她约会了
lt's too weird for you. l won't see her again.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我是说  过了明晚之后
I mean, after tomorrow night. -No, no, no!
不不不  求求你  我受不了
No, no, no! Please, I can't! l can't do it.
-我真的会捉狂  -好  好  好
- lt's gonna freak me out! - Okay, okay, okay!
好  我今晚就告诉她
Okay. l'll tell her tonight
我不能再跟她见面
l can't see her anymore.
谢了  罗斯
Ross, thanks.
你要我现在打给她吗
You want me to call her now?
不用  不用
Oh, no. No, no, no.
那样就太夸张了  不用啦  真不用
No. Come on, l mean, that's crazy. That's crazy.
怎样啊  你最近在忙什么  忙什么呢
So, what's going on with you? what is going on with you?
这个
Well....
我这学期可能会再开一堂课
l may teach another class this semester.
好  打吧  现在就打给她
Yeah. Do it now. Call her right now.
-我最喜欢这段了  -我也是
- This is my favorite part. - Me too.
你们知道什么更催泪吗
You know what's sadder than this?
《小鹿斑比》
Bambi.
那部片让我哭了三天
l cried for three days with that movie.
不  是两天
No, wait. Two.
第三天我妈自杀了
'Cause on the third day my mom killed herself,
我也有在哭那件事
so l was partly crying for that.
哭ET就算了
Well, that l can see crying over,
但《小鹿斑比》是卡通片呢
but Bambi is a cartoon.
斑比的母亲死了  你没哭吗
You didn't cry when Bambi's mother died?
动画师不再画母鹿了  的确很可怜
Yes, it was very sad when the guy stopped drawing the deer.
钱德勒  哭没什么不对
Chandler, there is nothing wrong with crying.
你不必老是那么男儿有泪不轻弹
You don't have to be macho all the time.
我也没这么硬汉啦
l'm not macho.
也对
Yeah, you're right.
我刚说这话的时候想啥呢
l don't know what l was thinking.
反正我就是没大哭过
l guess I just never really cried.
我不是那种会哭的人
You know, l'm not a crying kind of guy.
拜托  你总会遇见令你鼻酸的事吧
Come on, man, there's gotta be something that gets you choked up.
像...
like....
如果你看到一只三脚小狗呢
What if you saw a three- legged puppy?
我肯定会难过
l'd be sad, sure.
-但是不会哭  -好吧
- But l wouldn't cry. - Okay.
要是那只小狗说  "钱德勒勒救救我
What if the puppy said, "help me, Chandler.
其他的狗狗都欺负我"
all the other puppies pick on me."
干嘛哭  我发现一只会说话的狗  发财了
Cry? l just found a talking puppy. l'm rich!
我知道了  我会做了
l've got it. l have got it.
你小时候的照片
Pictures from your childhood.
看了一定哭死你
This'll get you going good.
那张是什么
All right, what's going on there?
那是一年级的家长会
Thar's parents' Day. First grade.
我和门卫马丁的合照
That's me with the janitor, Martin.
-你爸妈呢  -他们不想来
- Where are your parents? - They didn't want to come.
-钱德勒  -好可怜喔
- Chandler! - Poor thing.
这件事不会让你想哭吗
That story doesn't make you cry?
不会  我就是不会哭
No. Look, l don't cry.
这又没什么  好吗
lt's not a big deal, okay?
不  不好
No! lt's not okay!
一点也不好
lt's not okay at all!
你的心是死的
You're dead inside!
-请问一下  -怎么了
- Excuse me? - Yeah?
-你是菲比·布非吗  -是
- Are you Phoebe Buffay? - Yeah.
你可以帮我签名吗  我是你的头号粉丝
Can l get your autograph? l'm your biggest fan.
我的头号粉丝  我一直想见你呢  你好
You're my biggest fan? l've always wanted to meet you. Hi.
没问题
Sure. Yeah.
谢谢你
Wow. Wow, thanks a lot.
我只想说  你真的天赋异禀
l just want to say, l think you're really talented.
你是因为崇拜我才说这种好听话
You're just saying that because you're my biggest fan.
乔伊  好好招呼那个人
Joey, listen. Take good care of that guy. Okay?
他是粉丝
He's a fan.
再见
Bye.
你看过我演《我们的岁月》吧
So you saw me on Days of Our Lives, huh?
要我来一段德雷克·拉莫瑞医生吗
You want me to do a little Dr. Drake Ramoray for you?
我不知道你在说什么
l have no idea what you're talking about.
不过我刚拿到菲比·布非的签名呢
But l just got Phoebe Buffay's autograph.
你是菲比的迷
Oh. You're Phoebe's fan.
没错  她的电影我都看过
Oh, yeah. l've seen all her movies.
电影
Movies?
她可是菲比·布非  AV巨星
That was Phoebe Buffay, the porn star.
不是吧
l don't think so.
是  她演过《性玩具总动员二》
No, it was. She was in Sex Toy Story Two...
《女人国的劳伦斯》
...Lawrence of a Labia.
而我拿到了她的签名
And l got her autograph.
我在漫画店的朋友一定不会相信
The guys at the comic book store won't believe this.
甘瑟
Gunther?
以后别让那个人进来
Don't let that guy in here anymore.
他说菲比是AV巨星
He said Phoebe's a porn star.
说巨星太夸张了
Well, l wouldn't call her a star,
不过她的确很不错
but she's really good.
你应该去看她那部《G点神探》
You should check out lnspect Her Gadget.
说了你一定不信
You will never believe what just happened.
罗斯刚刚拒绝我了  连个原因都没有
Ross just totally blew me off, and he didn't even tell me why.
好吧
Oh, well.
亲爱的  忘掉一个男人最好的办法
You know what? Honey, the best thing to do to get over a guy
就是跟别人交往
is to start dating someone else.
我们公司有个鲍伯
Oh! There is a great guy
你一定会喜欢
you will just love at work, named Bob.
他是人力资源部的明日之星
He's a real up-and-comer in Human Resources.
谢谢你替我打气  瑞秋
You know, thanks, Rachel, for cheering me up.
但我才不要跟路人甲乙丙交往呢
But l'm not gonna date some random guy from your work.
不是路人甲乙丙  是鲍伯
Not random. Bob.
可能是因为我不够成熟
lt's probably because l'm not mature enough
不够聪明
or smart enough.
或许他不喜欢我的打扮
Maybe he doesn't like the way l dress.
不太可能的
No, that can't be it.
一定是我不够聪明
lt's really gotta be the smart thing.
我好笨
l'm so stupid.
我就是个美得冒泡的笨女人
l'm just this, like, incredibly pretty, stupid girl.
不是
No, honey.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  你知道罗斯为何取消约会吗
Okay. You want to know why Ross canceled the date?
是我要求的
Because l asked him to.
你要求的
You asked him to?
-为什么  -因为你是我妹妹
- Why? - Because you are my sister...
-而罗斯和我有过一大段过去  -我不懂
- and Ross and l have this huge history. - I don't understand.
-你想跟罗斯交往吗  -不想
- You want to go out with Ross? - No.
你不要他  也不准我拥有他
You don't want him, but you don't want me to have him?
人力资源部的鲍伯
You know, Bob in Human Resources....
你居然这样对我
l can't believe you did this to me!
你害我怀疑我的智商
You had me doubting how smart l was!
你害我怀疑我的穿着品味
You had me doubting my fashion sense!
这没什么  只是叫你不要跟罗斯约会
lt's not that big a deal. Just don't date Ross.
世上的男人那么多
There's millions of other guys out there...
你没有资格教我做事
You have no right to tell me what to do.
我不是在教你做什么
l'm not telling you what to do.
我是在教你不要做什么
l am telling you what not to do!
你为什么老是这么嫉妒我
Why are you so jealous of me?
吉尔  不是我嫉妒你
Oh, Jill. This is not about me being jealous of you.
是你在耍任性
This is about you being a brat,
不能吃还硬要吃
wanting what you can't have.
什么不能吃
Can't have?
我唯一不能吃的东西只有乳制品
Excuse me. The only thing l can't have is dairy!
行  行啊
All right, all right.
你现在别想跟鲍伯的机会了
Well, you just blew your chances at dating Bob!
-谁啊  -人力资源部的啦
- Who? - With Human Resources!
我会嫉妒她吗
I am jealous of her?
她以为她是谁  卡洛琳公主吗
I mean, who does she think she is, Princess Caroline?
你嫉妒卡洛琳公主啊
You're jealous of Princess Caroline?
我有自己的城堡吗
Do l have my own castle?
-菲比不在吧  -不在
- Phoebe's not here, is she? - No.
真好  你们租了片子吗
Great. Did you get a movie?
对  对啊
Yeah. Yeah.
但应该不是你们喜欢的那型
But l don't think it's the kind you're gonna like.
你该不会又租那种
You did not get more movies
会整晚消耗面纸的片子吧
that'll have us reaching for the tissues all night, did you?
也没错啦
Sort of.
伙计们  到底怎么了
Guys, what's going on?
菲比是AV女优
Phoebe's a porn star!
-什么  -对啊
- What? - Yeah!
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
《菲比·布非之吸穴鬼猎人》
"Phoebe Buffay in Buffay The Vampire Layer."
-天啊  这是菲比  -你在哪里租的
- My god! - That's Phoebe. Where did you get that?
布里克街的成人录影带店
Down at the adult video place on Bleecker.
我看到乔伊正要进去  就先跑进去躲着
And l saw Joey was about to go in, so l ran in ahead of him...
想吓吓他
...to surprise him.
然后再假装不知道他也在
Then l pretended that l didn't know he was in there.
天啊  我真是不敢相信
Wow. l mean, l just can't believe this.
真是知人知面不知心啊
You know, l mean, you think you know someone.
虽然我们知道菲比很神秘  但这也...
Even Phoebe, who's always been somewhat of a question mark.
这也太悲剧了吧
This is so bizarre.
不过也说得通
l guess it kind of makes sense, though. You know,
毕竟她的童年那么悲惨
She had such a terrible childhood.
我童年悲惨  也没去拍黄片啊
l had a bad childhood and l don't do porn.
对  但是你的心死了
Yes, but you're dead inside.
我还是拿去还了吧
l'd better take that back.
为什么  干嘛还了
What, why? Why?
我们不能看  那是菲比演的
We can't watch it. I mean that's Phoebe.
你说得对  我们不能  也不该看
Yeah, you're right. We can't, we shouldn't watch this.
没错  还回去吧
Absolutely not. That goes back.
-看一点好了  -前半段就好
- Maybe a bit. - How about just the first half?
这样是不对的
This is wrong, you guys!
菲比是我们的朋友
Phoebe's our friend!
-我不要看  -没错
- l'm not gonna watch it. - Yeah!
乔伊  真有义气
Good for you, Joe.
我就知道你在这里  纳斯佛拉吐
l thought l'd find you here, Nosferatool.
布非  你要把你的尖棍
Buffay, are you going to plunge your stake
深深插进我体内吗
into my dark places?
其实我有点希望是你来插
Actually, l was kind of hoping it would be the other way around.
等等  她的脚踝上是什么
Hold on a second. What's that on her ankle?
你居然是在注意她的脚踝啊
Her ankle is what you're watching?
很难看得出来
Well, it's hard to tell.
她能不能不要动了
God, if she would just stop moving.
她只是在尽本分
She's just doing her job.
你们这群变态
You sick bastards!
是刺青
lt's a tattoo.
怪了  菲比没有啊
That's weird. Phoebe doesn't- -
是厄休拉啦  那不是菲比
Wait, that's Ursula! That's not Phoebe!
是厄休拉
That is Ursula!
倒带倒带
Wait, wait!
我可以看了  快倒带
l can watch that! Rewind it! Rewind it!
你们在干嘛  天哪  我在干嘛啊
What's up? Oh, my God! What am l doing?!
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
《心灵鸡汤》
"Chicken Soup for the Soul"?
这张沙发背后是空的啊
There's no back to this couch.
你看它干嘛  你讨厌这种书
Why are you reading this? You hate this kind of stuff.
我想试试看嘛
Yeah, I know. l figured l'd give it a shot.
也许有某个故事能戳到我的泪点
I mean, maybe one of the stories may make me cry,
你就不会觉得我的心死了
then you won't think l'm dead inside.
你真有心
Oh, that's so sweet.
但钱德勒  你不会哭也无所谓啊  我爱你
Chadler, l don't care if you can't cry. l love you.
这话温暖了我空空如也的机械胸口啊
Oh, that makes me feel so warm in my hollow tin chest.
-别闹啦  -我是说真的
- Stop it. - No, I mean come on. Seriously.
相信我们到时候结婚
Think about it. We get married,
站在神父面前  我却是这个表情怎么办
l'm up at the altar and l'm like this:
我不在乎
l won't care.
因为我知道你内心会充满喜悦
'Cause l know that you'll be feeling it all in here.
-是吗  -当然
- Yeah? - Yeah.
要是有一天我们生小孩
And if we have a baby one day...
医生在产房把宝宝交给你
...and the doctor hands it to you in the delivery room...
而你没有哭  那又怎样
...and you don't cry, so what?
送他离家去上大学
And if we take him to college and come home...
回家第一次看到他的空房
...and we see his empty room for the first time...
而你却没反应...
...and you got nothing?
我也不在意啊
lt won't matter to me.
好吧
Okay.
那我就不再担心这事了
l won't worry about this anymore then.
要是哪天我死了
And then, you know, if l die...
久病弃世
...from a long illness.
你在写哀悼词
and you're writing my eulogy
结果打开抽屉  看到我留了一张字条写道
and you open the desk drawer and find a note from me that says:
"我会永远与你同在"
"l will always be with you"
而你还是挤不出一滴眼泪
and you still can't shed one tiny tear?
我会知道你的心早已泪流成河
l know you'll be crying a river inside.
-我好爱你哦...  -你是哪里有毛病啊
- l love you so... - What is wrong with you?!
-什么  -还什么
- What? - What?
你居然无法为亡妻流一滴泪
You can't shed a tear for your dead wife?
我在世时  特地预先留了字条给你呢
l left you a note from the beyond!
所以刚才都不是真心话吗
So you didn't mean any of that?
废话  你个死机器人
No, you robot!
死小孩
You damn kids!
再乱按电铃我就...
You ring my bell one more time and l swear- -
吉尔
Oh, Jill!
刚只是我跟邻居小孩在玩的小游戏啦
That's a little game l play with the kids down the hall.
他们越来越喜欢我了呢
They've really taken a liking to me.
有什么事吗
Uh, what...what's the matter?
瑞秋和我大吵一架
Rachel and l had a really big fight.
我可以进去吗
Can l come in?
我知道我们不应该再见面
I mean l know we're not supposed to see each other anymore.
我也可以接受
I'm okay with that.
只是我人生地不熟
l don't know anybody in this city
又很需要找个人谈一谈
and l really need somebody to talk about it.
好啊  怎么了
Of course. What happened?
我不想谈
l don't want to talk about it.
好
Okay.
-不过有件事会让我比较开心  -什么
- You know what might really cheer me up? - What?
什么事  再多看几张你的超酷幻灯片
Seeing some more of your super cool slides.
-真的吗  -那当然  我爱死了
- Wow, really? - Totally. l loved them.
你还可以继续讲解  那几种不同的沙子
You could finish telling me about the different kinds of sand.
没问题  你等一下
l'd love to. Wait right here,
我去拿投影机和讲义
l'll go get the projector and my notes.
太好了  谢谢你  罗斯  你真是好兄弟
Great. Thanks, Ross. You're such a good friend.
你们有看到吉尔吗  我到处都找不到她
Have you guys seen Jill? l can't find her anywhere.
-没看到  -罗斯在家吗
- No. - ls Ross home?
或许我打去问他好了
Maybe l'll call him and see if he's seen her- -
哪一位
Who is it?
是菲比...
lt's Phoebe...
菲比
..."Phoebe" !
天啊
Oh, God!
所以你在拍黄片
So you're making porn movies.
我没有
No, l'm not.
摄影机还在拍呢
We're still rolling!
你现在就在拍
You're making one right now!
菲比  快点
Let's go, Phoebe.
而且还用我的名字
And you're using my name.
对  有什么事吗
Yeah, can l help you with something?
菲比  快点
Phoebe, come on!
我在跟别人说话...  你是在叫她
Look, l'm talking right now. You mean her. Oh.
双胞胎的题材一向很卖
You know, twin stuff is always a real big seller.
什么
What?
我可以帮你
l could talk them into giving you...
谈到三十块钱
...thirty dollars.
不要！ 想都别想
No! No way! No!
而且别再冒用我的名字  你真无耻
And stop using my name! And shame on you!
你们全都很无耻  你们恶心死了
And shame on all of you! You're disgusting!
尤其是你那个样子
Especially you, with that!
幻灯片快好了
The slides are almost ready.
好
Yeah.
我知道还少了什么
l know what this is missing:
酒
Alcohol.
好  厨房有红酒  好的
Okay, there's wine in the kitchen. Oh, great.
-喂  -我妹妹为什么在你家
- Hello? - What is my sister doing there,
还有窗帘为什么拉上了
and why are the drapes shut?
好  瑞秋  你别激动
Okay. Rach, calm down, okay?
她心情很差  我们只是在聊天
She's really upset. We're just talking.
罗斯  她想藉由跟你发生关系
Ross, I think she's trying make something happen with you
来报复我
to get back at me.
所以她来  只能是因为要报复你吗
So that's the only reason she could be here, huh?
就不能是因为我很善于倾听
lt couldn't be that maybe l'm a good listener...
放的幻灯片又超棒吗
...and l put on a great slide show?
罗斯  是真的
Ross, l am telling you,
她在利用你来报复我
she is using you to get back at me.
我自己可以应付
l think l can take care of myself.
回头再聊  再见
l'll talk to you later. Goodbye.
是你姐打来的
That was your sister, actually.
她觉得你在利用我
She thinks you're just using me.
所以呢
So?
我刚去了厄休拉的公司
So l just came from the company Ursula works for.
不会连你也下海了吧
Oh, no, not you too?
不  我是去领菲比·布非的报酬
l went to get Phoebe Buffay's checks.
钱还挺多的呢
There were a lot of them.
妙啊
Nice!
而且我不必再亲自去领了
And l won't have to go back there anymore...
我留了我的"正确"地址
...because l gave them my "correct address."
太好了
That's great, but...
但别人会误会你是AV女优  你不困扰吗
lsn't it gonna bother you that people think you're a porn star?
不会  我有办法
Oh, no, l know how to handle it.
-是吗  -没错
- Good. - Yeah.
想知道你在哪里见过我
Trying to figure out how you know me?
给你一个提示  是黄片
l'll give you a hint. From porn!
没错  你的变态男朋友
Yeah, your pervert boyfriend
在黄片里见过我
watched me in a porno movie!
-瞧  -厉害啊
- See? - Yeah.
你对吉尔的看法或许没错
You may have been right about Jill.
我就知道  怎么了
l knew it! What happened?
她吻了我
She kissed me.
什么  你们接吻了
What? You kissed?
也许我们应该回避一下
Maybe we should give them some privacy....
我尽量不去亲她了  好吗
Look, l tried not to kiss her, okay?
听起来不像
Doesn't sound like it.
想不亲一个人
l mean that's pretty easy not to kiss someone.
不要亲就对了
You just don't...kiss them.
瞧  我们现在就没有亲嘴啊
See? Look at us right now, not kissing!
让我说完  好吗
Let me finish, okay?
她主动来亲我
She started kissing me...
我没有阻止
...and l didn't stop it.
我当时没用脑吧
l guess l just wasn't thinking.
是啊  没错  你没用脑
Yeah. That's right you weren't thinking.
老娘赏你点东西  让你动动脑吧
You know what? Let me give you something to think about.
听我说完
Hold on!
后来我一想  就把她推开了
But then l started thinking and l stopped the kissing.
谢谢你把舌头从我妹的嘴里缩回来
Well, thank you for taking your tongue out of my sister's mouth,
还来告知我啊
long enough to tell me that.
我是想到  如果我跟吉尔有怎样
Look, l realized if anything happened with me and Jill...
我们就再也不能有其他发展了
...then nothing could ever happen with us.
-什么  -我是说
- What? - No, l mean....
我不知道我们以后会如何
l don't know if anything is ever going to happen with us...
还会不会有什么
...again, ever.
但我不想断绝这个可能性
But l don't want to know that it never could.
于是我喊停
So l stopped it...
然后...她气得摔坏我的投影机
...and she got mad and broke my projector.
我都不知道该说什么了
l don't even know what to say.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我的天啊  你在哭吗
My God, are you crying?
这两个人为什么就是不能在一起啊
l just don't see why those two can't work things out!
好  我要走了
All right, l'm leaving.
因为有人一直要破坏我好心情
Cause l'm not spending one more day with someone
所以我不想待在这个地方了
who's out to sabotage my happy mood.
就是你  瑞秋
That's you, Rachel.
我知道
Yeah, l got that.
还有你  我投怀送抱
And you! l throw myself at you...
你却不要  你有够同性恋的
...and you say no? How gay are you?
你自己保重  吉尔
You take care, Jill.
-好  再见  -再见
- Okay, see ya! - Bye bye.
吉尔居然走了
l can't believe Jill's gone.
没办法  我一发不可收拾
l can't help it, I opened a gate!